nutribullet.co.za 2017-02-11

# Nutribullet Privacy Policy

### THE SUPERFOOD NUTRITION EXTRACTOR

**DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATION**

The clause headings in this document are for convenience only and not for interpretation purposes.

1\. “FastBox” means the FastBox division of Melbro Wholesale (Pty) Ltd, registration number 1999/023585/07.

2\. “Services” means any services available on or through this Website;

3\. “User” means any person who enters or uses the Website;

4\. Hyperlinks herein to legal documents should be deemed part of these terms and conditions in terms of section 11(3) of the Electronic Communications and Transactions Act, no.25 of 2002.

**UNDERTAKING**

FastBox shall take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information of Users in accordance with the provisions of the Protection of Personal Information Act, No. 4 of 2013

**COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

FastBox may electronically collect, store and use the following personal information of Users:

  * name and surname;
  * address;
  * title;
  * contact numbers;
  * non-personal browsing habits and click patterns;
  * e-mail address; and / or IP address.

FastBox's right to collect, store and use any information collected from Users, shall be exercised subject to the following conditions:

  * It shall not disclose personal information from Users unless the User consents thereto, or unless compelled to do so by law.
  * It shall be entitled to use and share any information that does not relate to any specific individual.

FastBox collects and uses the abovementioned personal information for the following purposes:

  * To communicate requested information to the User;
  * To provide Services to the User as requested by the User;
  * To authenticate the User;
  * To provide the User with access to restricted pages on a Website; and / or
  * To compile non-personal statistical information about browsing habits, click patterns, and access to the Website.

**COOKIES**

Personal information as detailed above is collected either electronically by using cookies or is provided voluntarily by the User. Users may determine cookie use independently through their browser settings.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

**ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The Promotion of Access to Information Act no 2 of 2000 gives you the right to access the information that we hold about you. Should you wish to be apprised of such details, please contact us using the contact details below.

**CONTACTING US**

We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Statement.  Please do not hesitate to contact us at [info@nutribullet.co.za](mailto:info@nutribullet.co.za "info@nutribullet.co.za")

 If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be inaccurate.
